[
  {
    "id": "524",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "EFS is a file storage service for ________?",
      "answers": [
        "EC2 instances",
        "EBS volumes",
        "Edge Locations",
        "CloudFront"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["EC2 instances"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "525",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With EFS, storage capacity is __________?",
      "answers": [
        "elastic",
        "fixed"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["elastic"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "526",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With EFS, storage can grow and shrink in which way, so your applications have the storage they need?",
      "answers": [
        "automatically",
        "through scripted action",
        "through manual action"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["automatically"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "527",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "EFS supports the Network File System version ____ protocol?",
      "answers": [
        "NSFv4",
        "NSFv5",
        "NSFv3",
        "NSFv2"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["NSFv4"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "528",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With EFS, you pay in which way?",
      "answers": [
        "you pay for the storage you use",
        "you pay in Gb blocks",
        "you pay for reserved amounts"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["you pay for the storage you use"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "529",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "EFS can scale up to ________?",
      "answers": [
        "terabytes",
        "petabytes",
        "gigabytes",
        "megabytes"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["petabytes"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "530",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "EFS can support ______ of concurrent VFS connections?",
      "answers": [
        "thousands",
        "hundreds",
        "millions",
        "trillions"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["thousands"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "531",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "EFS data is stored across __________?",
      "answers": [
        "multiple AZs within a region",
        "multiple AZs across multiple regions",
        "multiple regions",
        "within one AZ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["multiple AZs within a region"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "532",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "EFS which type of storage?",
      "answers": [
        "block based",
        "object based",
        "file based",
        "optical based"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["block based"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "533",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "EFS has which type of consistency?",
      "answers": [
        "read after write",
        "write after read",
        "eventual consistency"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["read after write"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "534",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "EFS volumes need to be within __________ as the EC2 instances they are attached to?",
      "answers": [
        "security group",
        "IAM policy",
        "access policy",
        "VPC"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["security group"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "535",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Several EC2 instances can access the same files on EFS (acting as a ___________)?",
      "answers": [
        "file server",
        "RAID array"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["file server"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "536",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 3",
      "question": "You can apply which types of permissions on your EFS mounted volumes?",
      "answers": [
        "user level",
        "file level",
        "directory level",
        "EC2 level",
        "ELB level",
        "Target Group level"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["user level", "file level", "directory level"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "537",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When you apply permissions to your EFS volumes, the permissions are applied across _________?",
      "answers": [
        "all EC2 instances that mount the volumes",
        "only the EC2 instances that apply the permissions",
        "all EC2 instances in the security goup of the EFS mounted volumes",
        "all EC2 instances in the AZ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["all EC2 instances that mount the volumes"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "538",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Lambda",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Lambda takes care of provisioning and managing the servers that you use to run your code?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "539",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Lambda",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 3",
      "question": "With Lambda, you don't have to manage which of these?",
      "answers": [
        "operating systems",
        "patching",
        "scaling",
        "cost",
        "APIs"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["operating systems", "patching", "scaling"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "540",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Lambda",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "You can use Lambda in which of these ways?",
      "answers": [
        "As an event-driven compute service where Lambda runs your code in response to events",
        "As a compute service to run your code in response to HTTP requests using the API Gateway or API calls made using the AWS SDK",
        "As a file system that you can mout to multiple EC2 instances",
        "As a load balancer that you can point to multiple EC2 instances running in multiple AZs",
        "As a database that you can use to store key/value pair JSON data"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["As an event-driven compute service where Lambda runs your code in response to events", "As a compute service to run your code in response to HTTP requests using the API Gateway or API calls made using the AWS SDK"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "541",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Lambda",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You can use Lambda to respond to events initiated from an S3 bucket or a DynamoDB table?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "542",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Lambda",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Lambda _______ automatically?",
      "answers": [
        "scales",
        "queues",
        "starts"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["scales"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "543",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Lambda",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Each Lambda invocation causes ___________?",
      "answers": [
        "a new instance of the function to run",
        "the request to queue up in the functions buffer"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["a new instance of the function to run"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "544",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Lambda",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 5",
      "question": "In which languages can you write Lambda functions?",
      "answers": [
        "C#",
        "Go",
        "Java",
        "Node.js",
        "Python",
        "C",
        "Scala",
        "Ruby",
        "Pascal",
        "Fortran",
        "COBOL"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["C#", "Go", "Java", "Node.js", "Python"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "545",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Lambda",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 4",
      "question": "Which of these can trigger Lambda functions?",
      "answers": [
        "API Gateway",
        "AWS IoT",
        "Alexa Skills Set",
        "Alexa Smart Home",
        "ELB",
        "Auto-scaling Group"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["API Gateway", "AWS IoT", "Alexa Skills Set", "Alexa Smart Home"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "546",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Lambda",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 4",
      "question": "Which of these can trigger Lambda functions?",
      "answers": [
        "CloudFront",
        "CloudWatch events",
        "CloudWatch logs",
        "Code Commit",
        "EBS",
        "Target groups"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["CloudFront", "CloudWatch events", "CloudWatch logs", "Code Commit"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "547",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Lambda",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 5",
      "question": "Which of these can trigger Lambda functions?",
      "answers": [
        "Cognito Synch Trigger",
        "DynamoDB",
        "Kinesis",
        "S3",
        "SNS",
        "EC2",
        "Snowball"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Cognito Synch Trigger", "DynamoDB", "Kinesis", "S3", "SNS"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "548",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Lambda",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With the API Gateway ____________?",
      "answers": [
        "each HTTP request causes a separate Lambda function instance to run, in parallel",
        "each HTTP request queues up at the one Lambda function, where they are processed sequentially"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["each HTTP request causes a separate Lambda function instance to run, in parallel"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "549",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Lambda",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 3",
      "question": "Lambda is priced based on which of these?",
      "answers": [
        "the number of requests",
        "the duration of the function's runtime",
        "the amount of memory you allocate to your function",
        "the copies of the function that are spawned",
        "the disk space taken up by your code"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["the number of requests", "the duration of the function's runtime", "the amount of memory you allocate to your function"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "550",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Lambda",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Lambda runtime has a max threshold of __________?",
      "answers": [
        "5 minutes",
        "1 minute",
        "10 minutes",
        "90 seconds"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["5 minutes"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "551",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Lambda",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You are charged for the duration your Lambda function runs ________?",
      "answers": [
        "from the time your code begins executing until it returns or otherwise terminates",
        "from the time your code begins executing to the 5 minute max",
        "from the time from when the system loads your code until the system terminates your code",
        "in 5 minute intervals"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["from the time your code begins executing until it returns or otherwise terminates"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "552",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Lambda",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You are charged for the duration your Lambda function runs rounded up to the nearest ______?",
      "answers": [
        "100 ms",
        "10 ms",
        "second",
        "5 seconds"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["100 ms"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "553",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Lambda",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Lambda scales _________?",
      "answers": [
        "within 100 ms",
        "within 10 ms",
        "instantly",
        "at the interval you configure"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["instantly"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "554",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Lambda",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Lambda scales _________?",
      "answers": [
        "out, not up, automatically",
        "up or out according to the parameters you set",
        "out, not up, at a preconfigured interval",
        "when programmed to do so",
        "up, not out, automatically"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["out, not up, automatically"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "555",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Lambda",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Lambda functions are _________?",
      "answers": [
        "independent, 1 event = 1 function",
        "dependent, 1 event queues at your 1 function",
        "preconfigured, 1 event = your predefined number of functions",
        "interdependent, 1 event = any number of functions"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["independent, 1 event = 1 function"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "556",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Lambda",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Lambda is _________?",
      "answers": [
        "serverless",
        "server bound"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["serverless"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "557",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Lambda",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 4",
      "question": "Which of these AWS services are serverless?",
      "answers": [
        "Lambda",
        "S3",
        "API Gateway",
        "DynamoDB",
        "EC2",
        "Elastic Beanstalk",
        "Lightsail"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Lambda", "S3", "API Gateway", "DynamoDB"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "558",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Lambda",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Lambda functions ____________?",
      "answers": [
        "can trigger other Lambda functions",
        "can't trigger other Lambda functions",
        "can have EFS volumes mounted to them",
        "can run in an infinite loop"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["can trigger other Lambda functions"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "559",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Lambda",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "1 event can trigger multiple Lambda functions if you program your Lambda functions to call other Lambda functions?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "560",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Lambda",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Architectures using Lambda can get extremely complicated, you can use _________ to debug what is happening?",
      "answers": [
        "X-Ray",
        "CloudWatch",
        "CloudFront",
        "CodeCommit",
        "CodeDeploy"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["X-Ray"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "561",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Lambda",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Lambda can do things globally, such as back up S3 buckets to other S3 buckets in other regions?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  }
]
